(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Blood boiling faster
than a light
Look, you're so
small, such a
sight Made of
metal in your
eyes I'll fuck
you up on
sight So many
things make me
mad I can't
do this, I
can't do that
You tell me
what to do
Fuck that, you
wish you could
control this us
Keep me enraged
Run from me,
really make haste
Vocabulary wasted And
keeping me enraged
These days I
wait Slippery slope,
slid in for
a do Wish
it was you
Body bare, I
wear armor Lose
your sleep In
the dead of
the night Over
me, I write
with a Knife
the size of
the dick of
my current man
Front of house,
they can't ignore
Your misgivings Are
you good enough?
Seems like I
caught you in
the act No
questions for a
song like that
Keep me enraged
Run from me,
really make haste
Your vessel, I
debase it Your
blood, all I
can taste Keep
me enraged Run
from me, really
make haste I
tear you into
pieces You're trash
and chastened These
days I wait
Slippery slope, slid
in for a
do Get my
wish up, stay
scared and hide
Look at yourself,
spoil such a
sight